A Guide to the Fairfax County Office of Public Affairs Photograph Collection, 1962-2009
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 6: Photo and Negative File, 1987-2006
  - Voluntary Action Center Awards - Kim Cook and Jeb Stuart High School Honor Society (Trapnell), 1994 May 9 (Box 12)
  - Major Ronald P. Milner (Bulova), 1994 May 9 (Box 12)
  - Bren Mar Park Elementary School (Trapnell), 1994 May 16 (Box 12)
  - Foster Care Month (McConnell), 1994 May 16 (Box 12)
  - Public Works Week (Davis), 1994 May 16 (Box 12)
  - Asian/Pacific Islanders Month (Davis), 1994 May 16 (Box 12)
  - Certificates for Problem Solvers-Glasgow Middle School (Davis), 1994 June 6 (Box 12)
  - Carleen Payne, Virginia Reading Teacher of the Year (Davis), 1994 June 6 (Box 12)
  - Tree Commission Members (Hyland), 1994 June 6 (Box 12)
  - Ray Watson Retiring Principal (Trapnell), 1994 June 6 (Box 12)
  - Ed Ryan Retiring Principal (Dix), 1994 June 6 (Box 12)
  - Nancy Poole Retiring Principal (Dix), 1994 June 6 (Box 12)
  - Lord and Lady Fairfax, 1994 June 6 (Box 12)
  - Onthank Awards, 1994 June 6 (Box 12)
  - Robinson High School Girls Soccer (Frey), 1994 June 27 (Box 12)
  - Langley High School Boys Tennis (Frey), 1994 June 27 (Box 12)
  - Centreville High School Girls Track (Frey), 1994 June 27 (Box 12)
  - Allison Henss - Firefighter (Hyland), 1994 June 27 (Box 12)
  - Edward Mooney (Davis), 1994 June 27 (Box 12)
  - Fairfax Fair (Davis), 1994 June 27 (Box 12)
  - Therese Cummo (Trapnell), 1994 July 18 (Box 12)
  - Ian Caldwell (Davis), 1994 July 18 (Box 12)
  - Rev. Bob Cilinski, 1994 July 25 (Box 12)
  - Cos Renzi (Hanley), 1994 July 25 (Box 12)
  - Gayl Carr (Davis), 1994 July 25 (Box 12)
  - National Night Out (Trapnell), 1994 July 25 (Box 12)
  - Diana Schmelzer (Dix), 1994 August 8 (Box 12)
  - Clifford E. Gaskins (Davis), 1994 August 8 (Box 12)
  - Springfield Mall Volunteers (Davis), 1994 August 8 (Box 12)
  - NACo Awards, 1994 August 8 (Box 12)
  - Fairfax Connector Kick-off Ceremony (Herndon/Reston), 1994 August 27 (Box 12)
  - POW Proclamation (Davis), 1994 September 12 (Box 12)
  - Jury Service Appreciation Week (Davis), 1994 September 12 (Box 12)
  - Channel 16 10th Anniversary (Davis), 1994 September 12 (Box 12)
  - James Williams (Retiree), 1994 September 12 (Box 12)
  - Reginal Williams (Reitree), 1994 September 12 (Box 12)
  - First Union Bank Volunteers (Hyland), 1994 September 12 (Box 12)
  - Brosar Village Hunting Creek Neighborhood Watch (Hyland), 1994 September 26 (Box 12)
  - William Enderle (Bulova), 1994 September 26 (Box 12)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month (Davis), 1994 September 26 (Box 12)
  - National Character Counts Week (Dix), 1994 September 26 (Box 12)
  - Mental Illness Awareness Month (Davis), 1994 September 26 (Box 12)
  - Lila Carnavell - Retiree (Alexander), 1994 October 10 (Box 12)
  - Northern Virginia Junior League (Davis), 1994 October 10 (Box 12)
  - Turn Off the Violence Week (Trapnell), 1994 October 10 (Box 12)
  - Darrell Winslow (Hyland), 1994 October 10 (Box 12)
  - Karen Disenbacher (Davis), 1994 October 10 (Box 12)
  - National Character Counts Week, 1994 October 19 (Box 12)
  - Substance Abuse Awareness Week (Davis), 1994 October 19 (Box 12)
  - Wal*Mart, Coastal America, United Community Ministries and Fairfax County Housing & Community Development (Alexander), 1994 October 31 (Box 12)
  - Francis J. Dutton (Davis), 1994 October 31 (Box 12)
  - Catherine Locke (Retiree), 1994 October 31 (Box 12)
  - Organ Donor Resolution (Davis), 1994 October 31 (Box 12)
  - Fairfax-Falls Church Community Services Board 25th Anniversary (Davis), 1994 October 31 (Box 12)
  - Rev. John T. O'Hara, 1994 October 31 (Box 12)
  - World AIDS Day, 1994 November 21 (Box 12)
  - Patrick G. Deegan, 1994 November 21 (Box 12)
  - Red-Out Day, 1994 November 21 (Box 12)
  - Russian Visitors from Langley High School (Bulova), 1994 December 5 (Box 12)
  - Naomi Zeavin (Davis), 1994 December 5 (Box 12)
  - Gum Springs History Week - Ron Chase (Hyland), 1994 December 5 (Box 12)
  - George Mason Day (Hanley), 1994 December 5 (Box 12)
  - Fairfax County Fire & Rescue - Swift Water Rescue Unit (Berger), 1994 December 12 (Box 12)
  - World Summit for Children - Michel F. Looney (Bulova), 1994 December 12 (Box 12)
  - Witch Watch GMU Students (Bulova), 1994 December 12 (Box 12)
  - Dick King - Retirement Resolution, 1994 December 12 (Box 12)
  - Tom Davis - Goodbye Resolution, 1994 December 12 (Box 12)
  - Chuck Moeser (Berger), 1995 May 1 (Box 13)
  - Michael Kerns & Mr. Yen (Hanley), 1995 May 1 (Box 13)
  - Asian Pacific Month (Hanley), 1995 May 1 (Box 13)
  - Older Americans Month (Hanley), 1995 May 1 (Box 13)
  - Mary Carter (Connolly), 1995 May 1 (Box 13)
  - Henry B. Latimer (Dix), 1995 May 22 (Box 13)
  - Joyce Tobias (Hanley), 1995 May 22 (Box 13)
  - Adopt-A-Cause Steering Committee (Bulova), 1995 May 22 (Box 13)
  - Springfield Days (Alexander), 1995 May 22 (Box 13)
  - Gun Turn-In Day (Hanley), 1995 May 22 (Box 13)
  - Public Works Week (Hanley), 1995 May 22 (Box 13)
  - Tanker Accident Recognitions (Bulova), 1995 June 5 (Box 13)
  - Hal Strickland (Hanley), 1995 June 5 (Box 13)
  - Women’s Center Day (Hanley), 1995 June 5 (Box 13)
  - Lord & Lady Fairfax, 1995 June 5 (Box 13)
  - Tree Preservation Task Force (Bulova), 1995 June 26 (Box 13)
  - Earth Day/Arbor Day (Bulova), 1995 June 26 (Box 13)
  - Community Corrections Resources Board (Hanley), 1995 June 26 (Box 13)
  - Benjamin Ettleman (Aluminum Cans Campaign) (F&R) (Hyland), 1995 July 17 (Box 13)
  - Officer Stephen Needles, Aaron Kush, Mark Royer and families (Connolly), 1995 July 17 (Box 13)
  - Keith Michael (Connolly), 1995 July 17 (Box 13)
  - Xerox and George Mason University Paralympic Trials (Berger), 1995 July 17 (Box 13)
  - Pamela Burns (Dix), 1995 July 17 (Box 13)
  - Mark Crain (Dix), 1995 July 31 (Box 13)
  - Reston Festival Organizers (Dix), 1995 July 31 (Box 13)
  - Viva Vienna Festival Organizers (Dix), 1995 July 31 (Box 13)
  - National Night Out (Trapnell), 1995 July 31 (Box 13)
  - Fairfax County’s Day of Appreciation (WWII Vets) (Connolly), 1995 July 31 (Box 13)
  - Richard Lockwood, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - Vincent Picciano, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - Northern Virginia Swimming League, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - West Springfield High School Girls Soccer Team, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - Vienna-American 9&10-year-old Little League, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - NACo Awards - Office of the Sherriff and Circuit Court, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - NACo Awards - Office for Children, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - NACo Awards - Fire and Rescue Department, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - NACo Awards - Office of Transportation, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - NACo Awards - Office of Management and Budget, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - NACo Awards - Department of Environmental Management, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - NACo Awards - Park Authority, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - NACo Awards - Office of Finance, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - NACo Awards - Fairfax County Public Libraries, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - NACo Awards - Department of Public Works, 1995 August 7 (Box 13)
  - Centreville High School Girls Softball Team (McConnell), 1995 September 11 (Box 13)
  - Turn Off the Violence Proc. (Hanley), 1995 September 11 (Box 13)
  - Katherin Marie Slimak (McConnell), 1995 September 11 (Box 13)
  - Robert Bean (McConnell), 1995 September 11 (Box 13)
  - Byron Waldman (Hanley), 1995 September 18 (Box 13)
  - Susan Plancheon (Hanley), 1995 September 18 (Box 13)
  - Nancy Spinks - Cardiac Arrest Program, 1995 September 18 (Box 13)
  - Maryanne T. Ibach (Dix), 1995 September 18 (Box 13)
  - Mary Preston Historical Society - Canadian Delegation (Hanley), 1995 September 18 (Box 13)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month Proc (Hanley), 1995 September 18 (Box 13)
  - Public Lands Appreciation Day Proc (Hyland), 1995 September 18 (Box 13)
  - Ribboncutting - Fairfax County Parkway I-66 to Braddock Road, 1995 September 19 (Box 13)
  - Golden Girls Softball Association (Hanley), 1995 October 16 (Box 13)
  - Disability Awareness Month Proc. (Hanley), 1995 October 16 (Box 13)
  - Breast Cancer Awareness Month and Mammography Day (Hanley), 1995 October 16 (Box 13)
  - Part Time Professional Day (Hanley), 1995 October 16 (Box 13)
  - Safe Today for Tomorrow and Save Today (Dix), 1995 October 16 (Box 13)
  - Character Counts Week (Dix), 1995 October 16 (Box 13)
  - Helen Wilson Community Room Dedication (Alexander), 1995 October 16 (Box 13)
  - Baba Freeman (Dix), 1995 October 16 (Box 13)
  - West Springfield High School Boys Cross Country Team (McConnell), 1995 October 16 (Box 13)
  - West Springfield High School Girls Swim and Dive Team (McConnell), 1995 October 16 (Box 13)
  - Substance Abuse Awareness Week (Hanley), 1995 October 30 (Box 13)
  - Motor Carrier Safety Inspection Program (Hyland), 1995 October 30 (Box 13)
  - Shop with A Sheriff Program (Hyland), 1995 October 30 (Box 13)
  - George Mason Friends Day (Trapnell), 1995 October 30 (Box 13)
  - Patrick Hanlon (Hanley), 1995 November 20 (Box 13)
  - MADD Red Out Day (Dix), 1995 November 20 (Box 13)
  - Native American Month (Hanley), 1995 November 20 (Box 13)
  - Worlds Aids Day - Dec. 1, 1995 (Hanley), 1995 November 20 (Box 13)
  - Ella Miller 115th Birthday (Dix), 1995 December 4 (Box 13)
  - Mary Gormley (Trapnell), 1995 December 4 (Box 13)
  - Joan Doyle (McConnell), 1995 December 4 (Box 13)
  - Bill Clay (Trapnell), 1995 December 4 (Box 13)
  - Tara Foose & Sally Peed (Dix), 1995 December 11 (Box 13)
  - Bob Lowery (Alexander), 1995 December 11 (Box 13)
  - MPO Robbie G. Cloyd (Alexander), 1995 December 11 (Box 13)
  - Office of Management & Budget & Edward L. Long, Jr. (Hanley), 1995 December 11 (Box 13)
  - Knox Singleton & Kenton Pattie (Connolly), 1995 December 11 (Box 13)
  - Inauguration Ceremony - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, 1995 December 30 (Box 14)
  - McLean High School Athletic Teams (Mendelsohn), 1996 January 22 (Box 15)
  - Fairfax County Youth Football Teams (Dix), 1996 January 22 (Box 15)
  - Accessible Garden Plots at Nottoway Park (Connolly), 1996 February 12 (Box 15)
  - Jack Massey - Retiree (Dix), 1996 February 12 (Box 15)
  - Black History Month - February (Hanley), 1996 February 12 (Box 15)
  - Junior League of No. Va. (Dix), 1996 February 12 (Box 15)
  - Swift Water Rescue Team (Mendelsohn), 1996 February 26 (Box 15)
  - Mavis Derflinger - Support of youth soccer (Hanley), 1996 February 26 (Box 15)
  - Women’s History Month - March (Hanley), 1996 February 26 (Box 15)
  - John Nelson - Volunteer Service to Fairfax County (Dix), 1996 February 26 (Box 15)
  - Judith Mueller, Executive Director, The Women’s Center (Mendelsohn), 1996 March 11 (Box 15)
  - Art’s Appreciation Day (Hanley), 1996 March 11 (Box 15)
  - Immunization Month., 1996 March 11 (Box 15)
  - Mental Retardation Awareness Month (Bulova), 1996 March 18 (Box 15)
  - Centreville Archaeological Excavation Exhibit (Frey), 1996 March 18 (Box 15)
  - Display Cases for historical artifacts (Connolly), 1996 March 18 (Box 15)
  - Fairfax Corner in Moscow-two Russian Visitors (Bulova), 1996 March 18 (Box 15)
  - 20th Anniversary Northwest Center for Community Mental Health (Hanley), 1996 March 18 (Box 15)
  - Public Health Week - April 1-7, 1996 March 18 (Box 15)
  - Building Safety Week (Frey), 1996 April 8 (Box 15)
  - Victims’ Rights Week (Dix), 1996 April 8 (Box 15)
  - Sudler Flag of Honor & Sudler Cup Award (Bulova), 1996 April 29 (Box 15)
  - National Safe Kids Week (Dix), 1996 April 29 (Box 15)
  - Lake Braddock Secondary Schools Girls Gymnastics Team (Bulova), 1996 May 13 (Box 15)
  - Robinson Secondary School Girls Basketball Team (Bulova), 1996 May 13 (Box 15)
  - Richard Bliss-Dranesville Dist. Rep./Fx. Co. Park Authority (Mendelsohn), 1996 May 13 (Box 15)
  - Golden Girls Softball (Hanley), 1996 May 13 (Box 15)
  - Older Americans Month (Hanley), 1996 May 13 (Box 15)
  - West Springfield High School Girls Swim & Dive Team (McConnell), 1996 May 20 (Box 15)
  - West Springfield High School Boys Indoor Track Team (McConnell), 1996 May 20 (Box 15)
  - West Springfield High School Boys Cross Country Team (McConnell), 1996 May 20 (Box 15)
  - West Springfield Chorus (McConnell), 1996 May 20 (Box 15)
  - Asian- Pacific American Heritage Month. (Hanley), 1996 May 20 (Box 15)
  - Public Works Week (Hanley), 1996 May 20 (Box 15)
  - Springfield Days (Kauffman), 1996 May 20 (Box 15)
  - Danielle Foard-only Va. Student to represent US in 3-city European soccer tournament (Connolly), 1996 June 3 (Box 15)
  - Christopher Browne, Christopher Roland, Katie Stanonik & Marianne Barrick-St. James Catholic School/” Seek Out Science” (Gross), 1996 June 3 (Box 15)
  - WT Woodson High School Girls Lacrosse Team (Connolly), 1996 June 3 (Box 15)
  - WT Woodson High School Boys Lacrosse Team (Connolly), 1996 June 3 (Box 15)
  - Oakton Elementary School/50th anniversary (Connolly), 1996 June 3 (Box 15)
  - Pine Spring Elementary School/40th anniversary (Connolly), 1996 June 3 (Box 15)
  - Sally Ormsby/” State Mother of the Year” (Connolly), 1996 June 3 (Box 15)
  - Carl Peed/Region One Director/’96 Law Enforcement Torch Run (Bulova), 1996 June 3 (Box 15)
  - Wilton H. Dickerson/Providence Dist. Rep./Fx. Co. Redevelopment & Housing Authority (Connolly), 1996 June 3 (Box 15)
  - Kenton Pattie-retiring as Pres./Fx. Co. Council of PTAs (Gross), 1996 June 17 (Box 15)
  - Greg Evans-Springfield Dist. Rep./Park Authority (McConnell), 1996 June 17 (Box 15)
  - Khoi Do-GMU scholarship (Kauffman), 1996 June 17 (Box 15)
  - West Springfield High School Outstanding Students (McConnell), 1996 June 17 (Box 15)
  - James Madison HS Varsity Girls Softball Team (Dix), 1996 June 17 (Box 15)
  - Chantilly High School-Group AAA Central Fidelity Cup (Frey), 1996 June 17 (Box 15)
  - Ribboncutting - Fairfax County Parkway - Lee Chapel to Hooes Road, 1996 July 2 (Box 15)
  - Carrington Williams - retiring as founding Chairman/Wash. Airports Task Force (Gross), 1996 July 8 (Box 15)
  - Karen Milligan-Fx. /FC Community Services Board (Hanley), 1996 July 8 (Box 15)
  - Tom Chadwick- retiring as Chairman/Fairfax County Consumer Protection Commission (Hyland), 1996 July 8 (Box 15)
  - Mary Alice Glenn- retiring as Community Outreach Coordinator/Reston Interfaith (Dix), 1996 July 8 (Box 15)
  - Col. Ross Rogers & Rita Rogers-Suder/education of children in the community (Dix), 1996 July 8 (Box 15)
  - Earth Day/Arbor Day (Bulova), 1996 July 8 (Box 15)
  - Gina Voss Edwards Day- reporter leaving area (Dix), 1996 July 8 (Box 15)
  - Langley High School Girls Softball Team (Mendelsohn), 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - Herndon High School Boys Soccer (Mendelsohn), 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - Herndon High School Boys Baseball Team (Mendelsohn), 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - McLean High School Girls Lacrosse Team (Mendelsohn), 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - “National Night Out” (Hanley), 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - “Mike Scully Day” (Dix), 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - NACo Awards - Park Authority for Nottoway Park Accessible Garden Plots, 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - NACo Awards - Purchasing & Supply Management Agency & Department of Information Technology for Information Network/Bulletin Board., 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - NACo Awards - Department of Environment Management for A New Approach to Plan Review, Permits & Inspection., 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - NACo Awards - Department of Tax Administration for Central Information Team (CIT) Merger., 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - NACo Awards - Community & Recreation Services for Saturday Morning Integrated Leisured Experience. (SMILE), 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - NACo Awards - Mental Health, Mental Retardation & Alcohol & Drug Services of Fairfax-Falls Church for New Generations., 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - NACo Awards - Department of General Services for Scheduled Repair & Maintenance (SCRAM) Team., 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - NACo Awards - Office of Management & Budget for 1995 Rental Housing Complex Census Analysis., 1996 July 22 (Box 16)
  - Porter Hutchison, Margaret Peck & Ray Birch present to each Board member a copy of the book, “Voices of Chantilly”. (Hanley), 1996 August 5 (Box 16)
  - J. Sidney Holland (Gross), 1996 August 5 (Box 16)
  - Carol Lindsay (McConnell), 1996 August 5 (Box 16)
  - William Castro (Hyland), 1996 August 5 (Box 16)
  - Bone Marrow Awareness Month (Frey), 1996 August 5 (Box 16)
  - James Lee Sports Club., 1996 August 5 (Box 16)
  - Hettie Hervey (Frey), 1996 August 5 (Box 16)
  - Lorraine Lavet (McConnell), 1996 August 5 (Box 16)
  - Roberta Holland Day (Hanley), 1996 August 5 (Box 16)
  - Lilyan Spero (Connolly), 1996 September 9 (Box 16)
  - Transportation Safety Commission (Connolly), 1996 September 9 (Box 16)
  - Vienna Little League 9/10 yr. old & 11/12 yr. old champions (Dix), 1996 September 9 (Box 16)
  - Commission for Women Day (Hanley), 1996 September 9 (Box 16)
  - James F. Jenkins (Hanley), 1996 September 9 (Box 16)
  - Save Today for Tomorrow Month & Oct.9, 1996 as Save Today (Dix), 1996 September 30 (Box 16)
  - Ecoloday (Hyland), 1996 September 30 (Box 16)
  - Lewis Leigh, Jr. (McConnell), 1996 September 30 (Box 16)
  - Franconia United Methodist Church - 100th Anniversary (Kauffman), 1996 September 30 (Box 16)
  - Northern Virginia Turn Off the Violence Week (Dix), 1996 September 30 (Box 16)
  - 4-H Week (Dix), 1996 September 30 (Box 16)
  - Virginia Women’s Network Month (Gross), 1996 September 30 (Box 16)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month (Hanley), 1996 September 30 (Box 16)
  - Eugenia Gratto Day (Dix), 1996 September 30 (Box 16)
  - Disability Employment Awareness Month (Hanley), 1996 October 14 (Box 16)
  - Character Counts Week (Dix), 1996 October 14 (Box 16)
  - VolunteerFest Day (Hanley), 1996 October 14 (Box 16)
  - Breast Cancer Awareness Month (Bulova), 1996 October 14 (Box 16)
  - Natural Resources Conservation Week (Hyland), 1996 October 14 (Box 16)
  - Native American Month (Hanley), 1996 October 28 (Box 16)
  - South Lakes HS Wind Ensemble (Dix), 1996 October 28 (Box 16)
  - Kevin Greenlief & DTA Staff (Mendelsohn), 1996 October 28 (Box 16)
  - Federal Fish & Wildfire Services - presentation of check to County, 1996 October 28 (Box 16)
  - Christine Sleeper (Mendelsohn), 1996 November 18 (Box 16)
  - Rick Wormeli (Mendelsohn), 1996 November 18 (Box 16)
  - Linda Hossenlopp (McConnell), 1996 November 18 (Box 16)
  - Economic Development Authority - 40th Anniversary (Hanley), 1996 November 18 (Box 16)
  - James Madison (Dix), 1996 November 18 (Box 16)
  - State Farm Insurance (Dix), 1996 November 18 (Box 16)
  - AIDS Awareness Day (Hanley), 1996 November 18 (Box 16)
  - Substance Abuse Awareness Week (Hanley), 1996 November 18 (Box 16)
  - Russian Delegation (Bulova), 1996 December 2 (Box 16)
  - Aluminum Cans for Burned Children Campaign (Hyland), 1996 December 2 (Box 16)
  - Gillian Kilberg (Mendelsohn), 1996 December 2 (Box 16)
  - Ecumenical Community Helping Others (McConnell), 1996 December 9 (Box 16)
  - Aubrey Tarkington (Frey), 1996 December 9 (Box 16)
  - Centreville High School Cross Country Team (Frey), 1996 December 9 (Box 16)
  - Medical Care for Children Partnership (Hyland), 1996 December 9 (Box 16)
  - Michael Belefski (Hanley), 1996 December 9 (Box 16)
  - Madison High School Football Team (Dix), 1996 December 9 (Box 16)
  - Reston East Park & Ride Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 1997 January 3 (Box 17)
  - Lorraine Foulds (Gross), 1997 January 6 (Box 17)
  - John DeNoyer, 1997 January 6 (Box 17)
  - Faith in Action (Bulova), 1997 January 6 (Box 17)
  - Robert Hartwell (Frey), 1997 January 6 (Box 17)
  - John A. Keating (Kauffman), 1997 January 6 (Box 17)
  - Justin Murphy (Dix), 1997 January 27 (Box 17)
  - Nick Hilgert (Bulova), 1997 January 27 (Box 17)
  - African-American History Month (Hanley), 1997 January 27 (Box 17)
  - Daniel Kerr (Dix), 1997 January 27 (Box 17)
  - Thoreau Eagles & Twain Twisters Soccer Team (Connolly), 1997 February 10 (Box 17)
  - Chantilly High School Football Team (Frey), 1997 February 10 (Box 17)
  - Luther Jackson Middle School (Connolly), 1997 February 10 (Box 17)
  - Officers Troy Payne & Gary Beavers (Connolly), 1997 February 10 (Box 17)
  - Cardinal Business & Professional Women (Bulova), 1997 February 10 (Box 17)
  - Stephen Danzig (Frey), 1997 February 10 (Box 17)
  - Connie Ring (Dix), 1997 February 24 (Box 17)
  - Annandale Christian Community in Action (ACCA)(Gross), 1997 February 24 (Box 17)
  - Mental Retardation Awareness Month (Bulova), 1997 February 24 (Box 17)
  - David Morales (Dix), 1997 February 24 (Box 17)
  - Women’s History Month (Hanley), 1997 February 24 (Box 17)
  - Michael Weiss Day (Hanley), 1997 March 10 (Box 17)
  - Leonard Gunsior (Dix), 1997 March 10 (Box 17)
  - Arts Appreciation Day (Hanley), 1997 March 10 (Box 17)
  - Immunization Month (Hanley), 1997 March 24 (Box 17)
  - Margaret Andino (Bulova), 1997 March 24 (Box 17)
  - Greg Tseng (Mendelsohn), 1997 March 24 (Box 17)
  - Citizen-of-the- Year Award presented to Hanley (Hyland), 1997 April 28 (Box 17)
  - Brad Galleher & Jeff Hudson - Lake Braddock SS Dive Team (Bulova), 1997 April 28 (Box 17)
  - Lake Braddock SS Girls Gymnastics Team (Bulova), 1997 April 28 (Box 17)
  - Asian-Pacific American Heritage Month (Hanley), 1997 April 28 (Box 17)
  - Master Police Officer William Wolf & K-9 Bosco (Kauffman), 1997 April 28 (Box 17)
  - Suzanne Manzo (Mendelsohn), 1997 April 28 (Box 17)
  - West Springfield High School Girls Basketball Team (McConnell), 1997 April 28 (Box 17)
  - West Springfield High School Swim Team (McConnell), 1997 April 28 (Box 17)
  - Logan Kleinwaks (Dix), 1997 April 28 (Box 17)
  - James Madison High School Forensics Team (Dix), 1997 April 28 (Box 17)
  - Carl Jeff Bianchi (Dix), 1997 May 12 (Box 17)
  - People to People Program (Frey), 1997 May 12 (Box 17)
  - Older Americans Month (Hanley), 1997 May 12 (Box 17)
  - Law Enforcement Month, 1997 May 12 (Box 17)
  - General District Ct. Volunteer Appreciation Week (Hanley), 1997 May 12 (Box 17)
  - Burke Centre Day (Bulova), 1997 May 12 (Box 17)
  - National Safe Kids Week (Hanley/Dix), 1997 May 12 (Box 17)
  - Steven Shepard (Mendelsohn), 1997 May 19 (Box 17)
  - Rhythm & Cheer All-Star Competition Team (McConnell), 1997 May 19 (Box 17)
  - Suzi Powell (Mendelsohn), 1997 May 19 (Box 17)
  - Public Works Week (Hanley), 1997 May 19 (Box 17)
  - Springfield Days (Kauffman), 1997 May 19 (Box 17)
  - National Stand for Children Day (Hanley), 1997 May 19 (Box 17)
  - Lords & Ladies of Fairfax Fair Sponsors (Hanley), 1997 May 19 (Box 17)
  - Channel 16 CableACE Awards (Hanley), 1997 June 9 (Box 17)
  - Connie Pettinger (Dix), 1997 June 9 (Box 17)
  - West Springfield High School Outstanding Students (McConnell), 1997 June 9 (Box 17)
  - Onthank Awards - 10 am presentation, 1997 June 9 (Box 17)
  - Leadership Fairfax (Frey), 1997 June 23 (Box 17)
  - David Birtwistle, 1997 June 23 (Box 17)
  - Bryn Pavek (Dix), 1997 June 23 (Box 17)
  - Thomas Hutchins (Dix), 1997 June 23 (Box 17)
  - Joan Kelly Ozdogan, 1997 June 23 (Box 17)
  - John Salama (Connolly), 1997 July 7 (Box 17)
  - Vera Mellen (Hanley/Dix), 1997 July 7 (Box 17)
  - Sheriff Carl Peed and Sheriff’s Office Volunteers (Mendelsohn), 1997 July 7 (Box 17)
  - Brian McNicoll (Dix), 1997 July 7 (Box 17)
  - Earth Day/Arbor Day (Bulova), 1997 July 21 (Box 17)
  - National Night Out (Gross), 1997 July 21 (Box 17)
  - Alan Caldwell (Hanley), 1997 August 4 (Box 17)
  - Police Auxiliary Unit (Gross), 1997 August 4 (Box 17)
  - MPO Dempsey Dee Wilson (McConnell), 1997 August 4 (Box 17)
  - Dan Meier (Frey), 1997 August 4 (Box 17)
  - Robert R. Spillane (Mendelsohn), 1997 September 8 (Box 17)
  - McLean Little League Sr. Girls All-star Softball Team (Mendelsohn), 1997 September 8 (Box 17)
  - Southwest Youth Association 13-Year-olds Baseball Team (Frey), 1997 September 8 (Box 17)